<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Dainton Copse Forest School CIC</title><link>https://dcforestschool.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Dainton Copse Forest School CIC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://dcforestschool.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://dcforestschool.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dcforestschool.github.io/about/</guid><description>About us Using a Forest School approach, Dainton Copse Forest School CIC runs nature-based activities for children and their families in our beautiful woodland environment. At Dainton Copse your children will develop an appreciation and knowledge of the natural environment through all four seasons. They will have loads of fun making wonderful memories and learning to respect and care for our environment. They will take part in woodland crafts, campfire songs, marshmallow toasting, hot chocolate drinking and, of course, have lots of time for free play.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://dcforestschool.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dcforestschool.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Contact Phone Sara - number Email email
Find us</description></item><item><title>Gallery</title><link>https://dcforestschool.github.io/gallery/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dcforestschool.github.io/gallery/</guid><description>Gallery Our Woodlands are full of places to explore, learn and play! A dedicated campfire site, livestock and woodlands make up our Forest School facilities! Mud Kitchen The Camp Our Goats The Woodlands</description></item><item><title>Our Team</title><link>https://dcforestschool.github.io/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dcforestschool.github.io/team/</guid><description>Our team text about the team and photos</description></item><item><title>Sessions</title><link>https://dcforestschool.github.io/sessions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dcforestschool.github.io/sessions/</guid><description>Sessions Little Chestnuts £9 per session 6 week program Birthday Parties Birthday parties in the woodland are great fun and we love helping you to celebrate! Plenty of fresh air, space to roam and - best of all - no birthday cake trodden into your carpet or crisps to sweep up when everyone has gone home!</description></item></channel></rss>